<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6/9/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33234</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:33:13 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33234</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["*Glingleglingleglingle.*"<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Hogfather]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/8/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33233</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 02:33:13 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33233</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["There should be a notice ahead of the movie that says 'This
movie is PG.  Can you read?  You are a Parent.  Do you understand what
Guidance is?  Or are you just another stupid toddler who thinks they're
an adult simple because they've grown older and, unfortunately, have
developed fully-functioning sexual organs?  Would you like some
committee somewhere to decide *everything* for you?  Get a damn grip,
will you?  And shut the wretched kid up !'"<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/7/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33232</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:33:13 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33232</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The librarian was, ex officio, a member of the college council. No-one had
been able to find any rule about orang-utans being barred, although they
had surreptiously looked very hard for one."<br><br>Unseen University politics at work - Terry Pratchett, Eric]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/6/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33231</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:33:13 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33231</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The only things known to go faster than ordinary light is monarchy,
according to the philosopher Ly Tin Weedle. He reasoned like this: you
can't have more than one king, and tradition demands that there is no gap
between kings, so when a king dies the succession must therefore pass to
the heir *instantaneously*. Presumably, he said, there must be some
elementary particles -- kingons, or possibly queons -- that do this job,
but of course succession sometimes fails if, in mid-flight, they strike an
anti-particle, or republicon. His ambitious plans to use his discovery to
send messages, involving the careful torturing of a small king in order to
modulate the signal, were never fully expanded because, at that point, the
bar closed."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Mort]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/5/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33230</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:33:13 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33230</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["Look, that's why there's rules, understand? So that you *think* before
you break 'em."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Thief of Time]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>