<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>6/7/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33214</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 02:31:35 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33214</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The librarian was, ex officio, a member of the college council. No-one had
been able to find any rule about orang-utans being barred, although they
had surreptiously looked very hard for one."<br><br>Unseen University politics at work - Terry Pratchett, Eric]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/6/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33213</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:31:35 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33213</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The only things known to go faster than ordinary light is monarchy,
according to the philosopher Ly Tin Weedle. He reasoned like this: you
can't have more than one king, and tradition demands that there is no gap
between kings, so when a king dies the succession must therefore pass to
the heir *instantaneously*. Presumably, he said, there must be some
elementary particles -- kingons, or possibly queons -- that do this job,
but of course succession sometimes fails if, in mid-flight, they strike an
anti-particle, or republicon. His ambitious plans to use his discovery to
send messages, involving the careful torturing of a small king in order to
modulate the signal, were never fully expanded because, at that point, the
bar closed."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Mort]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/5/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33212</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 02:31:35 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33212</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["Look, that's why there's rules, understand? So that you *think* before
you break 'em."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Thief of Time]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/4/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33211</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:31:35 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33211</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["Cats don't hunt seals. They would if they knew what they were and where to
find them. But they don't, so that's all right."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, The Unadulterated Cat]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6/3/24</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33210</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 02:31:35 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=33210</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The net software here did its meltdown trick again at the weekend (it
happens about once every six months -- if only everything was as reliable
as WordPerfect 4.2, which only chews up a novel about once every two or
three years...)"<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>